

07539327968

hello@libbyodai.co.uk

www.libbyodai.co.uk

Education

Sep 2017 - Dec 2017 Kingston University Msc Embedded Systems

Sep 2013 - July 2016 Bournemouth University **BA (Hons) Digital Media Design** First Class

Sep 2012 - August 2013 Bournemouth University BA (Hons) Computer Visualisation and Animation

Aug 2011 - May 2012 Leeds College of Art Foundation Diploma in Art and Design Merit

Sep 2009 - July 2011 Greenhead College A Level Mathematics - A Chemistry - A Spanish - B AS Level Art and Design - A Biology - A

Experience

November 2016 - May 2017 Shazam Entertainment Ltd Junior Regression Tester

May 2015 - September 2015 Rhythm Digital Ltd **Junior Developer**

Profile

My main interest is creating unique and memorable experiences. I specialise in integrating concepts from the physical world into digital products. Putting the user in the centre of my design approach to create elegant solutions.

University

Created projects from concept to design and development in a range of different technologies.

- Project manager for group projects
- Ran Portfolio Club; a society for side projects

Shazam

Ran regression tests as well as UX testing on new products.

- Trained new members of the team
- Took initiative in liasing with international departments to solve major bugs in production
- Oversaw project reporting using Agile principles.

Rhythm

Provided Graphic Design, Illustration and C++ programming for client projects.

- Produced demo application to showcase new Intel camera technology
- Provided illustration and graphic design work for interactive displays for the V&A and House of European History.

Key Achievements

- "Best in Performance Art" prize at Hacksmiths
- Graphic Designer for Team Romania for Roller Derby World Cup
- Won Best in Game Design on Adobe Generations course

Interests

I am a passionate rollerskater, playing in the roller derby British Champonships. I also coach people learning to roller skate and help clubs by creating promotional print and digital material. In the rest of my spare time I take part in hackathons and crochet clubs.

Skills

Web

HTML 5, CSS 3/4, Wordpress, Javascript - Node, PHP and No SQL databases WebGL and three.js

Design

Adobe Creative Suite Sketch Maya/Blender

Native

iOS - Swift Android - Java C++ - Cinder

Misc

Agile Matlab Postman JIRA Git/Gitlab/Github

See my projects on my website. References are available on request.